{
    "subject": "resource/The_Royal_Oui",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "File Under: Music",
    "human_readable": "The label of The Royal Oui is File Under: Music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8037468791007996,
            "question": "Under what category would you find information about The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6433243155479431,
            "question": "How is The Royal Oui categorized?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6163724064826965,
            "question": "In what section would you find information about The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.574180006980896,
            "question": "Where would you look for details about The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5611403584480286,
            "question": "What is the classification of The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5473407506942749,
            "question": "What type of work is The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5447108149528503,
            "question": "What type of media is associated with the label 'The Royal Oui'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5062078237533569,
            "question": "What is the general subject of The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4088054895401001,
            "question": "What genre of media is The Royal Oui classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38770803809165955,
            "question": "To which artistic discipline does The Royal Oui belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of The Royal Oui is File Under: Music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_271_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of media is The Royal Oui classified as?",
            "html": "dbpedia_271_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the general subject of The Royal Oui?",
            "html": "dbpedia_271_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media is associated with the label 'The Royal Oui'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_271_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_271_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about The Royal Oui, a musical duo. According to the text, they recently signed with Vancouver label - File Under: Music (Blackie and The Rodeo Kings, Dan Magnan). This confirms that The Royal Oui's label is indeed File Under: Music."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Ari Shine and Adrienne Pierce, who form the band The Royal Oui, signed with File Under: Music. This supports the statement that \"The label of The Royal Oui is File Under: Music.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}